[
	{
		"id": 1,
		"question": "1. The new managing director..............a more effective management structure",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. propose"
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. proposed"
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. proposal"
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "B"
	},
	{
		"id": 2,
		"question": "2. The weather.........for tomorrow is partly cloudy with a chance of slight rain",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. forecasts"
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. forecasted"
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. forecast"
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "C"
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"question": "3. J&B Co. will be.....................its new line of home appliances next month",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. introduce"
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. introducing"
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. introduces"
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "B"
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"question": "4. Mr. Radford, the plant manager, recently............a tour of the production plant for visitors from Japan",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. conduct"
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. conducted"
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. to conduct"
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "B"
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"question": "5. ..................the personnel department directly if you have any questions regarding your benefits.",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. Contacting"
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. Contacts"
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": " C. Contact"
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "C"
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"question": "6. The monthly business meeting which is hosted by the president......an important role in exchanging ideas",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. play"
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": " B. plays"
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. playing"
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "B"
	},
	{
		"id": 7,
		"question": "7. All requests for office supplies should be................to Mr. Park by noon",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. submitting"
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. submit"
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. submitted"
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "C"
	},
	{
		"id": 8,
		"question": "8. The company announces that it plans to...............several properties to expand its business",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. aquire"
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. acquired"
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. acquiring"
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "A"
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"question": "9. Though many restaurants in the area offer an extensive dinner menu, the quality of service...........considerably.",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. varies"
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. vary"
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. various"
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "A"
	},
	{
		"id": 10,
		"question": "10. To attract customers, discounted items should..............at the front of the store",
		"answer": [
			{
				"value" : "A",
				"text": "A. have displayed"
			},
			{
				"value": "B",
				"text": "B. displays"
			},
			{
				"value": "C",
				"text": "C. be displayed"
			}
		],
		"correct_answer": "C"
	}
]